# SARAH CLARK

#### FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

## **BASIC INFORMATION**

Full Stack Web Developer with a Bachelor of Fine Arts in Interior Design, and 11 years of professional experience in both entrepreneurial and corporate settings. Dedicated to learning, displays a strong business acumen, and passionate about the future in Web Development.

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTMI
- CSS
- JavaScript
- JQuery
- Bootstrap
- Express.is
- React.js
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- MySQL

#### SOFTWARE SKILLS

- Adobe XD
- Photoshop
- Visual Studio Code

## **CONTACT DETAILS**

11451 E Penstamin Dr. Scottsdale, AZ 85255

Phone: 312.504.5391

Email:

sarahchristinec85@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sarah-clark-7aba2514/

GitHub:

https://github.com/scclark85

Portfolio: sarahcclark.com

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Web Development Freelancer**

Scottsdale, AZ · April 2019-Present

- Drive SMB mobile-responsive projects using React, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Adobe XD, and more
- Manage front-end and back-end development, and client relations

#### **District Manager/Owner, Elements Massage**

Chicago, IL · 2013-Present

- Launched two locations from the ground up
- Led operations, HR and marketing to 120% membership goal
- Managed 40-person cross-functional team
- Currently transitioning out of the management oversight

## **Design Assistant, Debora Lynn Interiors**

Chicago, IL · 2012-2013

- Developed floor plans, renderings and samples
- Managed contractor and client communications

## Stone Designer, Marble Emporium, Inc.

Northbrook IL · 2011-2012

- Designed flooring and countertops for kitchen and bathrooms
- Drove new business with architects and designers
- Managed projects to client satisfaction, deadlines and budget

#### **Design Consultant/Assistant Manager, BoConcept**

Chicago, IL · 2010-2011

- Managed showroom displays, in-home consultations and event staging
- Achieved top-seller positions multiple times
- Created proposals with space plans, 3D images, and customized furniture pieces

#### **EDUCATION**

## **University of Arizona** (Coding Boot Camp)

Class of April 2019 Certificate For Full-Stack Web Development

# **Harrington College of Design**

Class of August 2008 Bachelor of Fine Arts in Interior Design